http://www.meritech.com/privacy-policy2?hsLang=en

Don't know where to start? We can help!
COVID-19 Info
Don't know where to start? We can help!
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
We respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal data. This policy explains in general terms how we seek to comply with regulation including but not limited to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and how we process your personal data through your use of the Meritech website, including any data you may provide when you request to be contacted, buy something from us, sign up for a newsletter, or interact in other ways with our website and company. From time to time we may update our Privacy Policy by updating this webpage.
Information We May Collect
When you use our website, fill out a form, send us an email, or otherwise interact with our company we collect, retain and update the personal information you provide to us and details about your interactions with the website. This information may include your name, email address, phone number, information about the company you work for, product/service interests and preferences, or other details provided to us at the time.
How We Use Your Information
We may process and use the information you provide in the following ways:
To enable us to meet contractual obligations if you buy something from us;
To allow us to accurately respond to your customer service requests;
To send you the content, related product information, services and offerings which you are most likely to be interested in;
To help improve our website in order to enhance your experience.
We will never sell your personal information to third parties. You will only be contacted by us to inform you about products, services or other matters relevant to your relationship with Meritech.
We use software to administer and run our business. Some of your personal information may be stored in these systems. We only use services that safeguard your privacy and do not allow your information to be shared with other users of the software. We will only send your personal information to third parties when it is necessary for us to perform the service you have requested or when it is within our legitimate business interest. If you have any questions about our use of your personal information not answered here, please contact us at cleantechinfo@meritech.com.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies, which are small files stored on your device through your web browser (if you allow it). Cookies enable us to recognise your browser, capture and remember certain information, and respond to you as an individual. You can set your browser to refuse all or some cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies.
We use this information to improve and customize your browsing experience and understand how users interact with our website.
Marketing
You may receive marketing communications from us if you have purchased products or services from us, filled out a website form, or registered for a promotion and you have not opted out of receiving these communications.
Our marketing emails include an opt-out link in the footer. You can use this link at any time to adjust your marketing preferences and to opt-out of receiving any future marketing communications. You can also contact us at cleantechinfo@meritech.com at any time to update your preferences.
When you opt-out of marketing communications, we may still use your personal data to communicate with you about a product/service purchase, performance of a contract, or in relation to financial transactions.
Links to Other Websites
Our website may contain links to third party sites or other online services. We are not responsible for the information and privacy practices of these third parties, they are subject to their own policies and procedures.
Data retention
We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.
Controlling Your Data
Under the GDPR regulations in the EU, you have the following rights in relation to your personal data:
Request correction of your personal data to correct any incomplete or inaccurate data;
Request erasure of your personal data when you desire;
Request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format.
If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, or you have any questions about your personal information, please contact us at cleantechinfo@meritech.com or send postal mail to Meritech, 720 Corporate Circle, Golden, CO 80401, USA, Attention: Privacy.
We try to respond to all legitimate requests within 30 days. We may need to confirm your identity and verify you have the right to access requested data as a security measure to ensure your personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it.
If you have any questions or concerns at all about your privacy or this policy, please email us at cleantechinfo@meritech.com or get in touch with us at http://www.meritech.com/contact/.
Search
720 Corporate CircleGolden, CO 80401Call Us: (800) 932-7707
Products
Handwashing Systems
Boot Washing Systems
Hygiene Solutions
Product Enhancements
Services
Copyright © 2019 Meritech Systems LLC  All Rights Reserved.
Terms • Privacy Policy • Warranty
